jordandesert.net 2016-10-22

# Jordan Desert Trips & Tours

## Privacy Policy

##### Non-Personal Identifiable Information Collected Automatically

When you visit the Jordan Desert Trips & Tours website, we may collect and store information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We may also record the name of your Internet service provider. We use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our sites.

##### Personal Data

There are also several opportunities on our websites for you to provide us with information about you and your interests, such as your name, mailing address and e-mail address. If you choose to share any personal information with us, we may store it and use it for marketing research and other marketing purposes.

The information you share with us may be used by JORDAN DESERT TRIPS & TOURS and its members. It may be used by our suppliers exclusively to provide services for JORDAN DESERT TRIPS & TOURS, and by our business partners exclusively to conduct joint marketing programs with JORDAN DESERT TRIPS & TOURS. 

**We will not share your personal information with other third parties for their independent use without your permission.**

##### Information We May Place Automatically On Your Computer's Hard Drive

Our website may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. So, when you come back to visit us again, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit.

##### Who to Contact

If you have previously submitted Personal Data through the Site and would like that information deleted from our records and database, please contact us at our email address: info@jordandesert.com

**We will use every reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files and confirm with you the deletion of your Personal Data.**

**Your privacy is important to JORDAN DESERT TRIPS & TOURS and we want you to know that the information we collect will be treated with care.**
